Jane Fonda papers SSC.MS.00477
Sophia Smith Collection
- Audiovisual materials, 1970-2014; 6; 37.88 linear feet (55 boxes)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: O.D.D. and Aitu Driving, Oil drum driving, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: O.D.D. and Aitu Driving, Untitled 3, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: O.D.D. and Aitu Driving, Untitled 2, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: O.D.D. and Aitu Driving, Untitled 3, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BE15 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BE2 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEIntroduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEDestroyed Church + Area, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BERuined churches art (DM 2), approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEOff speed-2 churches, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEBomb detonation lifts from cut, not numericised HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BENumericised trims, Bomb detonation HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BE2nd Day DMZ WS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEMen in Militia ₣9 5000, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEDestroyed churches + DMZ driving, Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEUntitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEDMZ, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BENumericised trims HDS, leaving corner stone DA, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEMOS Numericised trims, ₣ Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ + Driving, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEUntitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BE1st Day DMZ WS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEPR6 Outs DMZ, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Crossing the DMZ TA+BEDestroyed Church [ ? #2 and 3], approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: Titles and Subtitles, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 88)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: IPC-Jane Fonda, 767019, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: IPC-Jane Fonda, IPC T5991, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: IPC-Jane Fonda, Untitled, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: XV Ha Thinh→ Vinh 11 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: XV Ha Thinh→ Vinh Sunset Jeep, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: XV Ha Thinh→ Vinh Numericised Trims MOS GF0000 Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: XV Ha Thinh→ Vinh Cattle Crossing Road & Women Working, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: XV Ha Thinh→ Vinh Numericised Trim GE 0000 Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Medicinal Garden, Numericised Trims, TRK Heads, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Numericised Trims, Dong Ha Hosp. PIX HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Dong Ha Sync Outs, Hops. PIX HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Pt 1 [female symbol] MD, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, [female symbol] MD pt 11, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Medicinal Garden, Numericised trim PIX Heads; Medicinal Garden sync, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Dr. sync. Med needs, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Medicinal garden Sync Outs HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Dong Ha Hosp. SYNC OUTS TRK HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Numericised Trims, Dong Ha Hosp. TRK HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Numericised trim CC5000 HEADS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Doctor on medical needs SYNC OUTS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Medicinal garden SYNC OUTS TRK HDS, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, [female symbol] md pt II, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, Traus A, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no flile) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, 1 Untitled splice, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 89)
  - Introduction to the Enemy, motion picture recording: VII Dong Ha Hosp Trims, 6 Untitled splices, approximately 1974; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file)
  - On Golden Pond, motion picture recording: Reel 1, approximately 1981; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 91)
  - On Golden Pond, motion picture recording: Reel 2, approximately 1981; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 91)
  - On Golden Pond, motion picture recording: Reel 3, approximately 1981; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file) (Box 91)
  - BBC Omnibus, motion picture recording: BBC Omnibus Jane Fonda, approximately 1979; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file)
  - U.S. War Crimes in Vietnam, motion picture recording: U.S. War Crimes in Vietnam Fred Engelberg w/o 38937 War crimes, approximately 1955-1980; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Grapes of Wrath, motion picture recording: Grapes of Wrath, Reel 1, B&W, approximately 1940; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Grapes of Wrath, motion picture recording: Grapes of Wrath, Reel 2, B&W, approximately 1940; 1 items (16mm)
  - Grapes of Wrath, motion picture recording: Grapes of Wrath, Reel 3, B&W, approximately 1940; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Grapes of Wrath, motion picture recording: Grapes of Wrath, Reel 4, B&W, approximately 1940; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Lakota Woman, motion picture recording: Lakora Woman R-1, approximately 1994; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Lakota Woman, motion picture recording: Lakora Woman R-2, approximately 1994; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Lakota Woman, motion picture recording: Lakora Woman R-3, approximately 1994; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Lakota Woman, motion picture recording: Lakora Woman R-4, approximately 1994; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Lakota Woman, motion picture recording: Lakora Woman R-5, approximately 1994; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Lakota Woman, motion picture recording: Lakora Woman R-6, approximately 1994; 1 items (35mm); 1 items (no file)
  - Jane Fonda/Steps Ahead, Reel III, Master' 'Prime Time Stereo Master, Music Program on tracks 1+2, Number of tracks: 4, 4 TRK Stereo", 1983 December 2; 1 items (16mm); 1 items (no file)
  - A Special Need…A Special Education, approximately 1975-2000; 1 items (1/4" Audio Tape); 1 items (no file)
  - Jane Fonda Workout, "Yoga Workout" and "Stress Reduction", approximately 1975-2000; 1 items (1/2" Audio Tape); 1 items (no file)
  - Interviews/TV: 9 to 5: National Organization of Working Women, approximately 1973-2000; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items ( no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: The 175th Anniversary Seminar of the Emma Willard School: "Making Connections," Boston Massachusetts, 1988 October 19; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: AFI Salute to Gregory Peck, 1989 March 21; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: AJC Tribute to Jane Fonda, 1989 June 7; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Atlanta Project/Douglas High School Clip Reel, 1992 February 23; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Bill Moyer: Eye on America-Tape # 9, 1992; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS) (Box 77)
    Related manuscript materials are in Box 75 of this collection.
  - Interviews/TV: Bill Press-Commentary, 1988 June 17; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: CBS and ABC Local News Clips of Farm Hearings, approximately 1985; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: A Century of Women Show #1, approximately 1994; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: A Century of Women Show #2, approximately 1994; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: A Century of Women Show #3, approximately 1994; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 1 of 3, Exhibition Copy A, 1992 February 14; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 2 of 3, Exhibition Copy A, 1992 February 14; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: The Dollmaker, Part 3 of 3, Exhibition Copy A, 1992 February 14; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Donahue Show, 1972, Jane Fonda, 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Donahue Show, Jane Fonda, 1972 September 6; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Donahue Show, Jane Fonda, Master, 1972 September 6; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Donahue Show - Nelson Manela [sic] Interview, 1990 March 2; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Entertainment Tonite, Jane Fonda - Old Gringo, approximately 1989; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: "Eyes on the Prize II" - "The Time Has Come (1964-66)" Malcolm X, 1 hour, 1990 January; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Fire in Our House, approximately 1980-2000; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Fire in Our House, A MayDay Media Production, approximately 1980-2000; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Fonda Bio Dukakis on "Nightline", approximately 1988; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Fonda - F.T.A. Film 1970's, ABC News 20/20, approximately 1970-1979; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Fonda on Fonda, :08 :15 :30, 1991; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS) (Box 77)
    Related manuscript materials are located in Box 75 of this collection.
  - Interviews/TV: Fonda on Fonda, 46:11 minutes, 1991 July 2; 1 items 1/2" Video Cassettes (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 77)
  - Interviews/TV: Fonda on Fonda Premiere, 8:00 pm (ET), 1992 January 13; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Fonda on Fonda, TRT 2:50, 1991 December 23; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Fonda Revision, 1991 December 19; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: "F.T.A.", 1970; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: "Funny Is Funny" Jane Fonda Award Speech, Viewing Copy, Moffett-Lee Productions, 1989 February 27; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Galanty & Company, Hayden - "My Dad", Hayden for State Senate "My Dad", 1992 May 22; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Generation 2000: Changing Girls' Realities, 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Geraldo Show, Mothers Against Gangs, 1988 May 17; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Good Day Atlanta, 2002 April 17; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Good Morning America, Kristofferson on "Amerika" Dan Issacson, 1987 February 17; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Gregory Peck-His Own Man, approximately 1988; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Habitat for Humanity/RP = Brian Cabell, CNN, 1993 April 6; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Hot Flash! The Truth about Menopause, 9-10 pm, 1994 October 28; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: HWPC Pro-Choice Weekend, Media Clippings Stringout, 1989; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Hypnotist at Workout, approximately 1980-2016; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: IAS Show #1110, Jane Fonda, approximately 1980-2016; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: IAS Show #1110: Jane Fonda Line Cut Dub of 875611, 1 of 3 MVTC, approximately 1980-2016; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: IAS Show #1110: Jane Fonda Line Cut Dub of 875623, 2 of 3 MVTC, approximately 1980-2016; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: I.F.F.A. "Fly Right" with Jane Fonda, 1987; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: "Inside the Academy Awards," TNT Program Production, approximately 1971-1981; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Inside the Actors Studio Jane Fonda - Show #1110 Closed Caption Prot., 1 of 1, approximately 1971-1981; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: "Introduction to the Enemy", approximately 1974; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane, 1993 July 1; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda and Ted Turner, Lakota Woman, KNBC Ch 4, Weekend Entertainment Tonight, 6:00 pm, 1993 October 24; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda: Body Shaper Workout, 1986 January 14; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda - Gregory Peck, KNBC Ch 4, Today Show 8:38 am, KNBC Ch 4 Today Show 8:40 am, 1988 August 3-4; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda Interviews, Prime Time 9/9/93, The Today Show, 1993 September 14; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 78)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda on CBS Morning, 1994 March 15; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda on CNN, approximately 1980-2000; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda on CNN Morning News, n.d., approximately 1980-2000; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda/USSR Visit, 1) Jane Fonda/Soviet TV Show, 2) Gone w/ the Wind Premiere, 3) Kremlin Run (CNN), Jane Fonda/Soviet TV Show (plus: Gorbachev mtg., GWTW premiere, CNN pkg.-Kremlin Run), 1990 October 15-27; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda - V is for Vote PSA Rough, 2004 November 7; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Jane Fonda's Celebrity Comedy Fashion Show, Tape 3, Fundraiser shown on cable, May 1982 Jane Fonda's Prime Time Fashion Promo Tape - 1st cut; *Prime Time aerobics segment*, 1984 January 4; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: "Klute', approximately 1971; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Lakota Woman, Entertainment Tonight, 1993 November; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Larry King Show, IFFA, 1986 March 12; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Laura Lee Turner-Seydel/Jane Fonda, Hard copy (syndicated), KNBC-TV (NBC) Los Angeles, 7:30-8:00 pm, 1989 November 11; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: "Lois Gibbs and Love Canal", approximately 1978; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Lost Boys - 60 Minutes, approximately 2003; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Lost Children of Rockdale County, 1999; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: The Making of "We Are the World", approximately 1985; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Man from Atlanta – Ted Turner, approximately 1980-1989; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: "Muerte Accidental de un Anarquista", 1986 June 17; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Nat'l Geo "Vietnam: After the Fire", approximately 1988; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: "Old Gringo," Columbia Pictures, Code in picture, 1988 August 26; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Old Gringo, Columbia Pictures, Copy of August 17th version, 1988 August 23; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Old Gringo, Electronic Press Kit, Rough cut (Revised), 1) "A Video Diary" 2) "A Collaboration" 3) Questions & Answers 4) 'B' Roll Montage, 1989 July 13; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: The Old Gringo, Jane Fonda Interview, 45:00, 1987 October 27; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: "The Old Gringo" Jimmy Smits- "Arroyo', 1987 June 23; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: "Old Gringo," Part 1, 1988 November 4; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: "Old Gringo," Part 2, 1988 November 4; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV: Old Gringo Parts 1 & 2, 1988 October 13-November 21; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 79)
  - Interviews/TV, Old Gringo, Parts, 1, 2 & 3, 1990 April 4; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, "Old Gringo" Reels 1-14, 1988 December 12; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, "The Old Gringo" Rueben Blades (Origin. Master), 1987 September 24; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, "The Old Gringo" Tape #4 Jane Fonda Interview (w/ visible code), 1988 January 12; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, "Old Gringo" Unedited Material, 1989 June 15; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, P.Fonda/CNN Profile, Easy rider 25 yrs later, approximately 1994; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, P.M. Magazine Dodger Camp, 1986 January 15; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, "The Power of Mimi" 20/20, 1989 December 29; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Showtime Entertainment, Celebrity Close Up, Jane Fonda, Viewing Dub, 1990 September 18; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Sir! No Sir! A Film by David Zeiger, For Preview Only, 2005; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, "Stanley and Iris Premier" [sic], Waterbury, CT., This is dedicated to you Jane! We Love You, approximately 1989-1990; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Interviews/TV, Supreme Court Vacancy and Women, C-SPAN Videotape 187563-1, Part 1 of 1, 2005 July 11; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)
  - Sylvia Fuentes Interview with Jane Fonda, 1988 January 23; 1 items 1/2" video cassette (VHS); 1 items (no file) (Box 80)